http://www.amtamassage.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to Main Content
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the American Massage Therapy Association (AMTA) website and via email or other forms of communication.
Acknowledgement
By visiting the AMTA website (the Site) and providing information to AMTA, you are accepting and consent to the practices and provisions of our Privacy Policy.
Personal Information Collection
We may collect personal information from you in a variety of ways, including when you visit our Site, respond to a survey, complete a form, make a purchase, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available. You may be asked for name, title, organization, mailing address, email address, phone and fax numbers, credit/debit card information and other personal contact details (“Personal Information”). We also may collect information on your views and preferences as they relate to AMTA services.
Any and all Personal Information you provide to AMTA through this Site is provided on a voluntary basis, and how much you disclose is up to you.
In some cases, such as profile pages, user forums, and interactive Site features, any Personal Information you provide may become publicly available to other members and the general public and is not considered confidential. When you voluntarily disclose such Personal Information, that information may be collected and used by others, resulting in unsolicited messages from others. Where you have publicly posted Personal Information, AMTA is free to reproduce, publish, or otherwise use such information for any purposes.
Non-Personal Information
We may collect non-personal information about you when you interact with our Site.  Non-personal information may include information about the computer you are using to connect to the Internet (such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information) and about your browser.
How We Use Collected Information
AMTA may collect and use your Personal Information for legitimate business purposes, including the following:
To improve customer serviceInformation you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our SiteWe may use your information and feedback to improve our products and services.
To send periodic emailsWe may use your email address to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, surveys, related product or service information, etc.
To provide targeted services and content
Sharing Your Personal Information
We may share your Personal Information with business partners and other third parties to deliver content, materials, and services available on or through the Site and to provide you with products or services that may be of interest to you. When we do so, we may share, rent, or sell your name and/or mailing address. With the exception of vendors providing hosting, database management, and development services related to the operation of this Site, we do not share, rent, or sell your email address.
We may occasionally send you offers on behalf of third parties or promote such offers on our Site. If you do accept a third party offer or request additional information, the third party may collect other personal information directly from you. Once a third party has your personal information, it is governed by the third party’s privacy policy. We also may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any Personal Information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
AMTA also may provide Personal Information to third parties if AMTA reasonably believes that release of information is necessary to: 1) comply with legal requirements or legal process; 2) protect or defend the rights or property of AMTA; or 3) protect other users of the Site or the public.
Members
Members may have been assigned or have created a user name and password to be used for accessing portions of the Site. We maintain that information to allow you to access the Site and to maintain our relationship with you as a member or provide specific services to you.
AMTA expressly reserves the right to contact any member or other user regarding account status, renewals, or other matters relevant to subscription or service.
How We Protect Your Information
AMTA uses measures designed to protect against the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, or alteration of information provided over the Site.  However, we cannot guarantee the absolute safety of your information.  If you become aware of any breach of Site security or this Privacy Policy, please notify us immediately.
Choices You Have
You choose what information to supply to this Site.  Please share only information as is needed or that you believe is appropriate.  You are under no obligation to provide us with Personal Information, but without it we may not be able to respond to your request.
You have the right to access, delete, or update the Personal Information you submit through our Site, or to make any inquiries about the processing of such information. If you wish to do so, please contact us as described below. We provide individuals with access to their Personal Information where we believe appropriate, including in situations where you are entitled to access and correct your Personal Information under applicable data protection and privacy laws.
If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.
Cookies
When you visit our web site, a “cookie” may be placed on your computer to track your visit and help us to improve the Site. You may set your browser to refuse or disable cookies, but if you do so, some features of the Site may not function properly.
Children's Privacy
AMTA does not market its products or services to children. We do not knowingly collect information from Site users under 18 years of age.
Acknowledgement of Transfer of Personal Data
Our Site is hosted on web servers in the United States. If you are located in a non-U.S. jurisdiction, for example, in the European Economic Area, you agree that by providing your Personal Information, you consent to the transfer of such information to the United States, a jurisdiction that may not provide an equivalent level of data protection to the laws in your home country.
Links to Third Party Websites
The privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy are for our Site only. We are not responsible for, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to, the privacy practices of any other website(s) that you may link to through the Site.  We encourage you to seek out and read the privacy policy of each website that you visit.
Changes to this Policy
AMTA reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. Please frequently check the Privacy Policy and particularly before you submit additional Personal Information via the Site. All revisions to this Privacy Policy will be posted on the Site via link from the homepage. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your continued use of the Site following the posting of this Policy or any changes to this Policy is considered your acceptance of those changes.
If you have questions, contact:
AMTA500 Davis Street, Suite 900Evanston, IL  60201Toll-Free 1-877-905-0577info@amtamassage.org
This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 25, 2018.
